Oh, my.
Rocco.
If I tell you something,
you can never tell anyone,
okay?
>> I promise. Now, this is between us.
>> My life
was so much easier when my dad was in a
wheelchair.
>> What up, y'all? This is your boy Ace
here. Hey, what up, fam? To So Caps,
y'all. One of the things that I'm really
loving on the show is the way they're
building up
Scout and Rocco's relationship right
now. I'm really loving it. Really loving
how they're doing it. They're They're
starting to get to a point where they're
getting comfortable by by confessing
feelings like
the thing for Scout is she's getting a
chance to talk to You know, she's got a
chance to talk to somebody about how she
feels about her father.
And her father has been ridiculous since
he's been out of the wheelchair. I mean,
I think I like I said, I think he's been
even worse
than he was before, like
and he's pissing people off around town
again. So,
it is crazy stuff, man. But, if y'all
want to see the full scenes with Scout
and and Rocco from this episode, I also
got Charlotte and Danny.
I'm trying to figure out how if I'm
going to put
these separate in a separate video cuz
I've also
I'm going to do Michael and Tracy in a
separate video as well. So, I'm trying
to figure out how I'm going to do it,
but cuz I'm doing Sonny Jason and
uh
Jason and Sonny
um
Jason and Sonny and then
Did I say I think I meant to say Jason
and Carly. Uh their scenes
all in the video. And I think I Yeah, so
I think what I'm going to do is this. I
think I'm going to put
Tracy, Michael,
Rocco, Scout, Danny, Charlotte, Drew,
Alexis, and then yeah, all in the same
video. I think I'll do it that way. Just
so I can do two videos and that'll be it
on the Patreon. So, y'all can watch
those full scenes on the Patreon, you
guys, and all of the other full scenes
for the rest of the week with Willow and
Michael, that storyline
is all up right now. Link to the Patreon
is in the description box, you guys.
So, the last time I covered Scout and
Rocco earlier in the week, we got a
chance to cover when Scout uh pushed
Rocco to the pool. It was one of the
cutest things I've seen in a while
on the show. And that's why I said I
like how they're building their
relationship up.
Um
and so
but this was man, this was crazy right
here though.
But I'm glad Scout admitted it all
right? And like I said, Scout's getting
to a point where she feels really
comfortable
telling Rocco things that she probably
would keep a secret either to herself or
to other people.
Now, one of the things that she confided
in Rocco about was the fact that
how she's
you know, she was complaining about her
father and like and just how like he's
been keeping
Scout away from the people that she
loves in town.
And now he's trying to do it with Alexis
again and everything and Danny and
and uh Rocco understands cuz he see
what's going on with that. And so
Scout actually revealed to Rocco
that her life was much easier when he
was still in the wheelchair and not
being able to talk or move.
It's crazy that she says that, but I
don't think anybody's like taking it as
like
anything like let's be honest, she's
thinking that in her head, right? And
we'd be thinking that too. If we were in
Scout's situation, we'd be thinking that
all that same about our own
parents. Like we can't even trip and say
that we won't.
If Drew was like if our parents are
acting like Drew is right now, we'd be
thinking the same god damn thing.
And and the truth is her life more than
likely was easy.
>> [clears throat]
>> You know, she was with Alexis. She was
able to see her brother whenever she
wanted.
Um
and everything else like that was going
on her life.
Now, she missed her father as well when
she when he was in a wheelchair, but
there's that other side of Drew where
he's just so overprotective
of her
and you know, keeping her away from
other family members is just
it's crazy for her, right? Cuz she's you
know, she especially when her mother
died, she wasn't used to all of that and
so
I told y'all, man, when she grows up a
little more and she becomes a teenager,
she's going to
she's going to have a problem with that.
And I and I I talked about that a long
time ago. I I remember talking about
that on this channel maybe last year. I
said, "Man, the stuff that he's doing to
Scout right now,
she's not going to like it cuz she's the
type of person that loves her family.
She's just like Layla. Layla
Courtemanche, she's just like her.
She's also just like Emily.
You know, they both were all about their
family and bringing them together and
all of this other stuff.
And so
this doesn't work out well. Like that
whole this whole arrangement he's got is
not working out well. And those two are
going to clash one day.
You know what I'm saying? Like they're
And Scout Scout could get to a point see
Drew has to watch it to where Scout
could get to a day where she just
rebels.
And you don't want your daughter to
rebel.
You know what I'm saying? Like that
>> [snorts]
>> teenage daughters are hell, man.
You know what I'm saying? I never had a
teenage daughter in my home, but I I
I grew up with one, my sister, and
seeing and seeing just how teenage
daughters are,
it could be hell on a parent. So,
he don't want it to get to that point,
but he's getting it to that point where
she's going to rebel.
And he's going to have to deal with
that.
So, I hope Jules is ready.
I hope Jules is ready cuz we talked
about that in his conversation the other
day
with Scout, but I can't blame him on
what she said, man. I'm glad Rocco's
trying to help her cuz they did like a
whole little arrangement. They want to
meet each other again later after his
shift.
But, um yo, they came up with a whole
plan cuz
uh
Jules is going to pick her up. I might I
might do a video on that. We'll We'll
see when we get to it. But, going to
here to get it give me your thoughts
here. Make sure you go watch my
Charlotte and Danny video, too. That's
That conversation was an interesting
one. Give this video a like, share,
subscribe, you guys. Thank y'all for
watching this one. So, catch you guys.